let questions = [
    {
        question: "What color is Pikachu from Pokemon?",
        options: ["Blue", "Orange", "Yellow", "Black"],
        answer: "Yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most sold video game of all time?",
        options: ["Minecraft", "Persona 5", "GTA 5", "Skyrim"],
        answer: "Minecraft"
    },
    {
        question: "What console does Sony make?",
        options: ["Switch", "Steam Deck", "Xbox", "Playstation"],
        answer: "Playstation"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first video game ever created?",
        options: ["Tennis for Two", "Donkey Kong", "Super Mario Bros", "Pong"],
        answer: "Tennis for Two"
    },
    {
        question: "Which was the first ever video game console ever made and sold commercially?",
        options: ["NES (Nintendo Entertainment System)", "Magnavox Odyssey", "Atari", "Gameboy"],
        answer: "Magnavox Odyssey"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Sonics signature ability?",
        options: ["To cast magic powers", "To jump high and stomp on enemies", "To run really fast", "To play poker really well"],
        answer: "To run really fast"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Marios profession?",
        options: ["Chef", "Accountant", "Plumber", "Prince"],
        answer: "Plumber"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these video game series is known to be very hard?",
        options: ["Dark Souls", "Kirby", "Minecraft", "Mario"],
        answer: "Dark Souls"
    },
    {
        question: "Which game first introduced the character Waluigi?",
        options: ["Mario Party 3", "Mario Tennis", "Mario Kart: Double Dash", "Super Smash Bros Melee"],
        answer: "Mario Tennis"
    },
    {
        question: "What color is most associated with Nintendos brand?",
        options: ["Dark Blue", "Green", "Yellow", "Red"],
        answer: "Red"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a Nintendo console?",
        options: ["Switch", "Gamecube", "Xbox", "Wii"],
        answer: "Xbox"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the princess that Mario rescues time and time again?",
        options: ["Peach", "Zelda", "Samus", "Daisy"],
        answer: "Peach"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the most popular puzzle game of all time?",
        options: ["Warios woods", "Picross", "Dr.Mario", "Tetris"],
        answer: "Tetris"
    },
    {
        question: "What item does Mario use to power up?",
        options: ["Chaos Emeralds", "Mushroom", "Diamond sword", "Soul"],
        answer: "Mushroom"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a character from Team Fortress 2?",
        options: ["The Scout", "The Medic", "The Knight", "The Spy"],
        answer: "The Knight"
    }
]

//Default exporting
export default questions;